(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
- (BIRDS CALLING)
- (WATER LAPPING)
WOMAN: (OVER HEADPHONES)
Your story matters.
SUE: My story matters.
WOMAN: You are important.
SUE: I am important.
WOMAN: Your life
is unfolding beautifully.
SUE: My life
WOMAN: You are confident.
I am confident.
WOMAN: You are enough.
I am enough.
WOMAN: You are strong.
I am strong.
WOMAN: You are capable.
Hi.
Hello. Hi.
I'm picking up an order
for Sue Buttons.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
$23.50.
Oh. I'm sorry...
Uh. excuse me.
I think someone
forgot to finish the "E."
(CHUCKLES) It should say
"Happy Birthday. Sue."
Not... "Suc." (CHUCKLES)
Cash or credit?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
KARL: What are you wearing?
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE)
I'm not wearing anything.
Ooh. Naughty.
WOMAN: You stroking
that cock right now?
KARL: Oh. I gotta go.
But I'm still gonna
see you tonight. right?
Yes. you will. honey.
Oh. good. You're still here.
Hi. honey.
I thought you went to the gym.
I bought a cake.
Oh. Well. that's nice.
Yeah. well.
except it isn't really
- 'cause they messed it up.
- (PHONE RINGING)
They misspelled my name.
Who can't spell "Sue?"
- Hello.
- NANCY: Hey. Sue. Where's Karl?
He's in the den.
You want me to get him?
No. no. I'm just calling
to remind him about the loan.
Okay.
The station goes under.
I'm on your couch. Sue.
Okay. But did you call
about anything else?
NANCY: What else
would I be calling about?
SUE: Well. just think about it.
What day is today?
- Tuesday?
- (CAR HONKING)
Na... Nancy.
you should come over
for dinner tonight.
I don't eat dinner anymore.
I'm on the air in 15 minutes.
I gotta go.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You are important.
You are strong. You matter.
(MOUTHING)
Karl. if you don't want
my sister moving in...
MAN: (ON TV) ...and thrive
to financial freedom.
Raised in a barn?
Bye!
WOMAN: (ON TV)
Your story is important.
Your story matters.
And I'm here to here to help.
So. what's your story?
I'm Gloria Michaels.
and I'm on your side.
In heartbreaking news.
13-year-old Emma Rose
is still missing.
Her parents spoke at
a news conference this morning.
EMMA'S MOM: I know
that my Emma is out there.
And I know
that I'm gonna see her again.
EMMA'S DAD: Emma. we love you.
I can't wait
for you to come home.
SUE: (WHISPERS) There you are.
EMMA'S DAD: We have everything
ready for you. okay.
(SIGHS)
Come on home
to Mommy and Daddy.
- Sue.
- We love you.
We love you so much. Emma Rose.
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MOUTHS)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Sorry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hello?
Hi. this is Sue
at Sidewinder Safety Tubs.
My colleague had to step away
for a moment.
I look forward
to solving your problems.
Who do I have the pleasure
of speaking to?
MAN: Go fuck yourself.
(SOFTLY) Okay.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
(SIGHS)
What did you just put
in your back pocket?
Are you stealing from us?
- No. What?
- (GASPS)
DEBBIE: Oh. Rita. Rita!
- Honey.
- Mm.
Remember how we agreed
that you wouldn't
scream my name
unless you were dying
or receiving pleasure.
You see that little felon
you hired?
He's stealing from us.
I am not.
I... I swear I am not.
I saw you put the phone
in your pocket.
PETEY: My crappy old phone.
Looks like one of these
brand new phones
sealed in a box.
and tied up in security wire.
Honey bear. it appears you
were wrong and should apologize.
Oh. look at that.
I gotta tow.
(PETEY CHUCKLES)
See you at supper.
- RITA: All right.
- Hey. Rita. listen.
I really do appreciate
this job.
- I know.
- And I swear I do not steal... anymore.
But listen.
it's okay if you still wanna
commit crimes
every now and then.
No. I don't. I do not.
But if you ever need a partner
for one of your crime jobs.
promise you'll consider me.
(CHUCKLING) What? No!
Oh. what. you think
I'm too old? Huh?
I'm robbing people
every day in here.
Look how much
I'm charging for this shit.
Uh. I appreciate
the offer. Rita.
but when Jonelle got pregnant.
I swore that I'd quit.
I'm about to be a daddy.
And I figure it's time
I stop stealing stuff
and start being
a model citizen.
There is nothing exciting
about being a model citizen.
I mean. we do the same
boring shit every day.
- and then you die.
- Hmm.
JANET: I mean. it's really sad
that young girls
can't leave their homes anymore
without some sick pervert
snatching them up.
It's a crazy world.
Oh. did you say something?
Yes. I did.
I said it's a crazy world.
(EVERYONE CHEERING)
(TUNE OF "HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO YOU" PLAYING)
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
(CONTINUES SINGING IN SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday. dear Janet
Happy birth... ♪
MAN: Bonjour. La Femme Aimée.
Hi. I would like to make
a dinner reservation
for two people tonight.
We have a table
for two at 8:30.
Gosh. that's awfully late.
Do you have anything...
- No.
- Okay. That-that's fine.
The name is-is Buttons.
Sue Buttons.
- Yes.
- Okay. got it.
I hear your place
is very swanky...
We have you down for 8:30.
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- Okay.
You cannot be here.
You get us Karl.
you get to retire.
Wasn't that the deal. Petey?
Well. it sure was.
And I hooked you up
with Karl. so...
MINA: We went to
the bank today. Petey.
And guess what?
Karl doesn't work there anymore.
Well. that is weird
because he should...
Have a seat.
- (SIGHS)
- We treated you okay. Petey.
- Yeah.
- We gave you work. paid you well.
And after all the kindness
we showed you.
you wanna leave us.
Come on. Mina.
But you said
you had a money guy.
You remember that.
right. Petey?
My dad is not a patient man
when it comes to his money.
- So where's Karl?
- I don't know.
(GRUNTS)
He switched branches!
He's at the Stanlow Bank
on Clark and Forth.
It took one minute to sell
out your brother? One minute?
RITA: Let him go!
Or I'll shoot you in the face
with this gun.
What. are you gonna
blow off my big toe?
No. your face.
Okay. well. right now
you're at my kneecap.
You gonna kneecap me?
That's my vagina.
You gonna shoot me in the vagina?
No. I respect that area.
Yeah. you respect that area?
(GRUNTS)
PETEY: Rita!
It's not nice
to point guns at people.
RAY: Let's go.
MINA: Obviously. this has been
a very frustrating morning.
- This is my frustrated face.
- PETEY: (GROANS) Okay.
And I don't want
to be frustrated anymore.
- PETEY: Yeah.
- So do us a favor.
and don't tell Karl
we're coming.
'Cause I'd hate to come back
if he disappears again.
Sure! (GROANS)
(PANTING)
Did you see that?
Yeah. are you okay?
You're bleeding.
I can't believe
I was in a street fight!
- I feel so alive!
- All right. calm down.
This is not a game.
And where'd you get a gun?
I found it in
the Whole Foods parking lot.
Looks good on me. right?
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hi. How can I help
you two today?
Hi. we're looking for Karl.
Are you currently
banking with us?
Because if not.
I'd be happy to help you
set up some new accounts.
We're looking for Karl.
All right. Well. listen.
if you need a loan.
or if you have any other
financial questions.
my name's Steve.
and numbers are my thing.
We're looking for Karl.
Oh. okay. Well...
(GROANS)
Ow. Okay. Well. he's just. uh...
Just down over there.
Just... He's the third office
from the left. so...
Good grip there. (CHUCKLES)
MINA: We're not happy. Karl.
KARL: Hey.
I didn't see you come in.
I was just looking for
something in the trash.
A receipt.
You changed branches.
Yeah. Didn't I tell you?
I. uh... I sent you an e-mail.
Must've gone to
your spam folder.
Would you rather have one eye.
or one ear?
I don't want
to do this anymore.
I could lose my job.
I could go to jail!
- (UNZIPS ZIPPER)
- RAY: Three million.
Jesus!
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I can't wash all this!
(GROANS)
I swallowed my tooth!
He swallowed his tooth.
Let's see.
Oh. dear.
Clean accounts by tomorrow.
Karl. I'm sorry to barge into
your place of work...
(SIGHS) but you are taking me
to dinner tonight.
You are not working late.
because it's my birthday.
Answer your damn phone. Petey.
Petey. I don't know how. they...
they found me at the new bank.
I can't do this anymore.
The money
is not worth this shit!
(SIGHS)
Karl. you forgot my birthday.
and I forgive you.
But you are
taking me to dinner.
(SIGHS)
Oh. I thought you forgot.
(SIGHS) Oh. Sue.
you ruined the surprise.
You ruined it.
It's okay.
I can act surprised.
(GASPS)
Oh. honey. I love the flowers!
Thank you so much.
I love them.
Where are we off to. stud?
What in the world?
WOMAN: Honey. hurry up!
KARL: Hey. baby.
WOMAN: Oh. I been waiting
for you for too long.
KARL: Coming to get ya.
- WOMAN: Hurry up.
- KARL: Oh. look at you.
I got you some flowers.
(GRUNTS)
WOMAN: I'm gonna stick those
flowers in a vase right here.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTING)
(SOBBING)
I am strong.
I'm important...
I'm strong... (SOBBING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hello. dear.
Would you like a room?
I actually lost my key.
My husband and I
are in room 14.
It's my birthday.
And he got me flowers.
(CHUCKLES)
Men just don't give flowers
like they should.
Not your husband. though.
A true gentlemen.
Here you go.
Happy birthday. sweetie.
Thank you.
WOMAN: Get in there!
Come on! Work!
- Deeper.
- (KARL GRUNTING)
WOMAN: Harder! Karl!
- Karl.
- KARL: Sue?
(GROANING)
WOMAN: Oh. my God! Karl!
Oh. God!
- Oh. my God! (SOBBING)
- Stop it!
Stop! Stop it!
No. please! I have kids!
I have kids.
What is your name?
- Leah...
- Leah.
Can you put your tit away?
- My tit... my tit.
- Put it away.
Thank you.
- (SNIFFS)
- Karl... is he okay?
Is he okay?
Karl...
Karl?
No. Leah. he's dead.
(SOBBING)
Oh. my God! Oh. my...
Stop it! You stop it!
I am important.
I am strong.
I am enough.
- Don't you think so. Leah?
- Yes.
I think so. too.
But I don't think Karl
thought so. but look at him now.
I'm not gonna say anything.
Oh. really. that your vagina
killed my husband?
I don't imagine you will.
(CRYING) No. I didn't...
Stop it!
(CRYING)
I'm sorry I hit you.
But I'm gonna take care
of everything. okay?
So here's what
I need you to do.
I want you to go.
Go?
Yeah. go on.
Get your things and go.
I'll take care of it all.
Don't forget your bra.
Karl. you forgot my birthday.
I need to cancel a dinner
reservation for two tonight
under the name Buttons.
My husband isn't feeling well.
so we won't be able
to make it.
Thank you.
(TV PLAYING INDISTINCT)
Karl. what am I
gonna do with you?
The search continues
for 13-year-old Emma Rose
who disappeared last...
GLORIA: You have been through
a month of hell
and unspeakable heartbreak.
and now the entire world
is behind you.
How has
the local community been?
The love they've shown to us
is truly remarkable.
EMMA'S DAD:
The letters of encouragement.
and people
have brought us food.
Thank you to Yuba County.
EMMA'S MOM:
Thank you. America.
GLORIA: You matter.
and your story matters.
I'm here to help.
I'm Gloria Michaels.
and I'm on your side.
MALE ANCHOR: Coming up next.
a Channel Five exclusive.
An interview
with the obstetrician
who delivered Emma Rose.
Please...
Help me!
My husband is missing!
(CRYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(QUIETLY) Excuse me. Officer?
Officer? I need to fill out...
- Have a seat.
- I'm sorry. Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
- Excuse me...
- (GASPS)
Don't you fucking touch me.
OFFICER: Okay. wait a minute.
Lawrence. come back here.
- OFFICER: Yes. ma'am.
- (DOOR OPENS)
I don't know
Hello. Detective Harris.
HARRIS: We got a busload
of teen assholes coming in.
Will you take him
to booking for me?
JONES: All right.
come on daddy's boy.
- let's go to jail.
- Detective...
I'm sorry.
how much longer? I...
OFFICER: Harris.
Detective. I-I need to fill out
a missing person report.
Okay. well. miss.
I don't handle that.
But my husband. Karl.
he's missing!
Well. when was
the last time you saw him?
Yesterday.
All right. so.
in situations like this.
we recommend checking in
with family and friends first.
I can't tell you
how many times.
husbands that go
out of town for the weekend.
and they don't tell
their wives.
- But I...
- Harris. our bus is here.
- Shit. Already?
- JONES: Yeah.
- I know he...
- Hey. let me go. huh?
Hey. let me go!
Who are you?
- (SUE GASPS)
- Ma'am. you need to leave.
Hey! Hey!
- (SCREAMING)
- JONES: Let's go!
- What are you gonna do. lady?
- MAN: Harris!
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- (YELLING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
ANNOUNCER: (ON TV)
The Gloria Michaels Show.
Voted Kentucky's number one
news and current affairs show
for the third year running.
Because she cares.
The Gloria Michaels Show.
GLORIA: Welcome back.
I've made a decision.
I am going to report
on no other story but yours
until we bring Emma Rose
back home.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING ON TV)
A commitment to you.
And Emma.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING
Here again
is your heartbreaking...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCT)
Shut up!
EMMA'S MOM: ...because of
how long it's been.
but I know that my Emma...
Fucking shut up! (YELLS)
Shut...
(TEAPOT WHISTLING)
(YELLS. SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
NANCY: I swear to God. Lennie.
if I don't get an interview
with the Roses.
I will lose my shit!
Karl! You forgot to put in
my loan application!
Oh. my God.
Sue. what happened?
Someone. um.
destroyed my house.
Do you know who?
- Sue.
- (CRYING)
Sue?
- Oh. Lord. Hey. hey.
- I don't...
Okay. all right. Oh. boy.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Okay.
Where's Karl?
- He's gone.
- What?
I woke up this morning and...
I think someone took him.
Who would take Karl?
Uh...
- Sue?
- I. uh...
Okay. did-did...
did you call the police?
SUE: I went... (CRYING)
I went to the police.
but they wouldn't help.
Are you serious?
Well. um. do...
do you know who
maybe would've taken him?
(SOBBING) I don't know.
I don't know.
- I don't know. I don't know!
- (NANCY MUTTERING)
I don't know what to do.
The police said wait 48 hours.
Maybe he. you know. went out
of the town for the weekend.
But-but just look at this place.
- Look at it!
- Uh-huh.
Something bad happened.
I need people
to be looking for Karl now.
but nobody knows he's missing.
so how can anybody find him
if they don't know he's missing?
Sue...
Let me help you.
How?
Have you seen
the Emma Rose story?
Is that the missing girl?
(WHISPERS) Yes.
I can do that...
for you.
I can get the public aware.
so they are looking for him
just like they are with Emma.
Sh-should we go
a bigger news station?
Like Gloria Michaels?
No. Sue.
No. we shouldn't.
Because they wouldn't give you
the attention that you deserve.
But I will.
Because you're my sister.
I'll take care of all of this.
- Okay? Okay.
- Okay.
Hey. Lennie. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Just get the crew together. Now.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
Nancy. we could get in
a lot of trouble for this.
We'll call the police
after we get the shot. okay.
- MAKE-UP ARTIST: Okay.
- NANCY: Okay.
- Ready?
- MAKE-UP ARTIST: Mm-hm.
Great. great. great. Hey.
Hi. Sue.
Hi.
You're gonna do great.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
You. uh...
(WHISPERS) You sad?
Yes.
Yeah. you are. aren't you?
You feel like crying?
Yes.
Okay. okay. You should... Okay.
Okay. roll. Let's roll.
Let's roll.
- We got it.
- (MAN CLEARS THROAT)
One. one.
One-two. one-two. one-two.
Two. one...
NANCY: (ON TV)
Local banker Karl Buttons.
abducted from his home
in what appears to be
a violent struggle.
Karl's wife. Sue Buttons.
woke up early this morning
to find her kitchen destroyed
and her husband missing.
Local police have yet
to respond to the incident.
- Sue...
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hey. babe.
- JONELLE: Petey. Karl's in trouble.
- What's wrong?
- Turn on Channel Two News.
Rita. turn the TV's
to Channel Two.
If you have any
information...
RITA: Do you know these
broads?
...on the disappearance
of Karl Buttons...
Oh. shit.
they kidnapped my brother.
- Should I get my gun?
- NANCY: Where we'll be...
I'll get my gun!
Oh. it's go time!
Sue. is there anything
you want to say to the people?
SUE:
I know you're out there. Karl.
I know I'll see you again.
(MUTTERS)
(SOBS) Ooh.
Okay...
This is Nancy Livingston
for KTV Two News.
You can cut.
Sue. you did great.
Oh. okay. Okay.
Okay.
- Here they come.
- Mm!
What the fuck is all this?
What the fuck is all what?
You say something?
MAN: Hell nah.
Mm...
(HARRIS CLEARS THROAT)
Nancy. KTV Two News.
We know.
- This is Officer Jones.
- Nancy.
Mrs. Buttons. uh. usually.
in a missing person case
people call the police
before they call the media.
She tried.
I was...
NANCY: Mmm-hmm.
(CHUCKLES) Uh. may we
look around. please?
It's just right through here.
When was the last time
you saw your husband?
- Yesterday morning.
- JONES: Mm.
HARRIS: Where's your kitchen?
Oh. um. sorry.
it's just right though here.
HARRIS: Okay.
Now be careful.
watch your step.
It looks like there was
some kind of a struggle.
I mean. with all this stuff
thrown about.
That's how I knew
something bad had happened.
But you said missing.
not abducted.
What?
Oh. I got it from here.
thank you.
Thank you.
Uh. you said missing.
This morning at the station. you didn't...
you didn't mention a struggle.
Well. I tried to tell you.
But then all those
teenagers came in.
and then no one
would listen to me.
- Hm.
- When did you realize your husband was missing?
This morning.
When I woke up.
I realized Karl
hadn't come home last night.
And then I came down
and saw the kitchen
and the great room and-and...
- And I knew something was wrong.
- Mm.
You didn't notice the kitchen
or the great room last night?
No. I...
Well. it was my birthday.
and we had dinner reservations
at La Femme Aimée.
That swanky new
French restaurant downtown.
But I was exhausted
when I got home.
so I went upstairs to close my eyes
for a minute and do some affirmations.
and I knew something was wrong
'cause Karl never woke me.
And I came downstairs.
and then I saw this.
and Karl was gone.
What'd you say?
- "Affirmations?"
- Yeah.
"You are worthy. you are loved.
you are special."
Uh. can you think of anyone
that that might want to harm
your husband?
Oh. my goodness. no.
I mean. I-I don't think so.
Karl was such a sweet man.
Why would anyone take him?
This is a photo of me and Karl
in case you need it for all the
press conferences and whatnot.
Okay. Great.
Yeah. we will do
everything we can to find him.
Can I get coffee or...?
No. no. no.
I only take my coffee in the morning.
NANCY: Hey.
HARRIS: You see how she kept
talking about him
in the past tense?
She's a little weird.
but that woman is definitely
not a criminal mastermind.
Yeah.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What did you do
with my brother. man?
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (GROANING)
No bodyguard today.
huh. Petey?
Fuck! I swear
I didn't mean any disrespect.
Ow. ow. you guys are so scary.
I would never do anything
to mess with you.
You know this.
(GRUNTS)
Thank you.
Guys. listen.
I know Karl messed up.
but he's real sorry. you know.
and it's not gonna happen again.
So. why don't you
just let him go. please?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Come on. Karl's missing.
I know you got him.
He's okay. right?
You didn't hurt him
or anything.
Um. we don't...
Oh. come on.
just tell me what you want.
What do you want?
What do you want?!
Twenty grand.
Where am I gonna get 20 grand?
That's a personal
Petey problem. So. tick-tock.
Goddamnit.
(LAUGHING.
MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
Looks like I'm about to make
some easy cash.
We don't have Karl.
So?
So. where is he?
And where's
your daddy's money?
BOY: Whoa. Whoa!
Whoa.
(BOYS LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
People don't fear you.
He took my money
because he thinks
he can get away with it.
He thinks he can
get away with it
because he doesn't fear you.
Mina. I can't trust you
to handle my business
if people don't fear you.
She's just a girl.
I expected more from you.
Hey!
Oh. hey!
STEVE: Well. hello.
Good to see you two again.
Steve.
Stanlow Banker of the Year.
Actually. uh.
Karl's not in right now.
(GRUNTS) Hey!
Well. I think
you two should leave.
I'm calling security.
Oh. my God.
Please. I live with my mother.
okay? She's very sick.
I have to give her medication.
I bathe her.
You bathe your...
Shut up!
- Please don't kill me.
- I should.
Imagining you
bathing your old ass mother.
The soap and everything...
Nasty.
What do you...
What would you like?
What do you want?
RAY: Was any money deposited
into any of these
accounts yesterday?
I'd be happy to check
account balances for you.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- (TYPING)
Thank you for choosing
Stanlow Community Bank
for your banking needs.
So it would appear that all
of these accounts are empty.
He took the money.
You wouldn't happen
to have any idea
where your colleague Karl is.
would you?
No. Uh. he didn't
come in for work today.
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
So. I... I don't know.
He's a new team member
at this branch.
so I'm not too familiar
with his schedule yet.
(STEVE GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
What?
JONES: Uh. no recent activity
on any of Karl's credit cards.
Last purchase he made
was a bouquet of flowers.
He buys a bouquet of flowers.
He's forcibly taken
from his kitchen.
Well. where are the flowers?
Maybe the kidnappers
took them.
- Stop it.
- Okay.
Or maybe he never
made it back home.
Knock. knock. We got a body.
- Karl?
- MAN: No.
But the body was found
in his office.
(JONES SIGHS)
- Shit.
- JONES: Yeah.
Here's the surveillance footage
you requested.
And screenshots
with all the people
who Steve was last seen with.
HARRIS: Missing banker Karl
and dead banker Steve.
There are a lot
of bad things happening
to the bankers at your bank.
And this is the picture
you give me?
We've never had
any trouble here.
So. updating the surveillance
system wasn't cost effective.
Let's see if Steve agrees.
- Come in here.
- (MOUTHING)
Hey. Steve. do you agree?
Nope. Steve doesn't agree.
Because Steve is dead!
And this shitty image
won't help us
catch the people
who killed him!
(SOBBING) I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to Steve.
Come here.
He can't hear you from there.
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry. Steve.
(SIGHS)
You matter.
Your story is important.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(FLAPPING LIPS. VOCALIZING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Miss Michaels.
(CONTINUES FLAPPING LIPS)
May I help you?
My name is Sue Buttons.
And I want to give you
an exclusive story
to play on the news.
Well. you can drop off
any potential stories
at the front desk.
I'd love to talk with you.
You can drop off
any potential stories
at the front desk.
It's a missing person story.
Is it a missing child?
No. it's my husband.
Karl Buttons.
My assistant will take
your story and your information.
If you follow me
up to the front
I can take your information.
Thirteen-year-old
Emma Rose is...
Emma Rose.
What?
She's the reason
my husband is missing.
Karl figured out
who took Emma Rose.
He was gonna tell the police.
and I think that's why
he was taken.
I think if you help me
find Karl...
we'll find Emma.
- (SNIFFLES)
- GLORIA: And you're sure
he said the name Emma Rose?
Yes. That morning.
he made me breakfast.
and while we were eating
he said.
"I know who took Emma Rose."
Why didn't you
immediately call the police?
I didn't think
anything of it. I...
I don't watch TV. so I hadn't
heard about poor Emma Rose.
I only heard her name when
I was in your station today.
and that's when I put
two and two together.
Even if you didn't know
who Emma Rose was.
if one of my husbands
says to me
he knows who
took somebody. anybody.
you better believe
I'm gonna ask questions.
I know. and I-I so wish I had.
but you-you have to understand.
Gloria. my husband...
He's a... conspiracy theorist.
He's always saying things like
he knows
who killed JonBenét Ramsey
and he knows who
kidnapped Natalee Holloway.
GLORIA: (ON TV) Is there a link.
between the disappearance
of Sue's husband Karl.
and the disappearance
of 13-year-old Emma Rose.
Uh. ma'am.
Do you know
if a Peter Buttons works here?
- (ZIPPER CLOSES)
- (GUN COCKS)
Are you stealing from me?
(WHISPERS) Hey...
Hey. Rita.
This ain't what it looks like.
Um...
After all I did for you?
- Are you stealing from me?
- (MOUTHING)
- Rita. Rita...
- (GUN CLICKS)
Rita! Fuck you!
- (LAUGHING)
- Oh! Fuck you.
But real talk.
- you stealing from me?
- Hmm.
Hey. Rita! The police is here.
Looking for the felon.
Shit. What?
What did I tell you?
What's going on back here?
- Nothing.
- Uh. nothing.
Nothing. You tell
the officers he'll be right out.
(PETEY PANTING)
Come on. Rita.
you called the cops?
Look. I am sorry.
but I need money to pay Karl's ransom.
And I was gonna pay you back.
I swear.
Hey. I'm no rat.
Then why are they here?
Have you committed
any other crimes lately?
Can I help you?
- Peter Buttons?
- Yeah. Petey.
We're here about Karl.
His wife reported him missing.
Yes. Yeah. uh.
I saw that on the news.
Well. when was the last time
you spoke to Karl?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Um. I want to say a week or two.
- You know...
- Mm. Which is it?
You want to say it.
or you're saying it?
I'm saying it.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. okay.
You and Karl close?
Well. yeah. he's...
He's my brother. so...
But you haven't talked to him
in a week or two?
Well. no. I've-I've
been busy with work.
and I'm having twins.
Can you think of someone
who might want to
harm your brother?
No.
No. no. Is there anything else?
'Cause I do...
I gotta get back to work.
Well. we're trying
to find your brother.
Yeah. of course.
Whoa. check this out.
HARRIS: Somebody turn that up!
(CLICKS)
I know. and I so wish I had.
but you have to understand.
Gloria. my husband...
He's a conspiracy theorist.
He's always saying things like
he knows
who killed JonBenét Ramsey.
and he knows who
kidnapped Natalee Holloway.
Well. it looks like
we won't need
to hold that press conference.
When was the last time you
talked to your sister-in-law?
Sue's...
Well. she's kinda quiet.
We don't talk that much.
SUE: He knew something.
Give me a call
if you remember anything else.
GLORIA: ...between the disappearance
of Sue's husband Karl...
- HARRIS: Last thing.
- Yes?
What was Karl's favorite
conspiracy theory?
What?
Call me if you hear something.
all right?
Okay.
HARRIS: Congratulations
on those twins!
- Thank you very much.
- It's a lot of work.
(CHUCKLES) Sure is.
Hey. kid. sorry about
your brother getting kidnapped.
I can't believe the same
people who took Emma Rose
also took your brother.
I mean.
what a crazy coincidence.
No. Rita. Mina and Ray
have taken Karl hostage
and are holding him
for ransom. okay.
Oh. yeah. that makes more sense.
Where am I gonna get 20 grand?
I guess
we gonna have to steal it.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Fuck.
SUE: Roberta? Janet? Hey.
We saw you on Gloria Michaels.
I'm so sorry about Karl.
So sorry.
You're not alone. So not.
I made you chicken tetrazzini.
I know it's hard.
but you have to remember to eat.
- Yummy.
- (ALL CHUCKLE)
JANET: Poor thing.
So brave.
Sue.
Hi. Jonelle.
Oh. my goodness.
When did this happen?
Hello in there.
I'm your Aunt Sue.
You know. I never heard Karl
talk about JonBenét Ramsey.
Natalee Holloway.
Why Emma Rose?
Oh... Well. you and Petey
don't visit us much.
so it's not surprising
that we don't know
what's happening
in each other's lives.
Did Karl walk out on you?
Excuse me?
Karl isn't the guy
who gets kidnapped
because he cracked
a missing girl case.
He's the guy
who runs off on his wife
and disappears
to start a new life.
And if your husband of 30 years
just up and walks out
on you one day.
I can understand faking
a kidnapping to save face.
Better a missing husband
than a deadbeat one. right?
If anything
ever happened to Petey...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...I would be supporting you
through the worst moment
in your life.
But I suppose
we have different ideas
on what it means to be family.
Petey is my family. Okay.
And he has finally gotten
his life together.
He is on a good path
and I refuse to let this
throw him off.
If this whole
kidnapping thing is fake.
then. Sue.
you need to come clean.
You're hormonal.
so I'll forgive the insult.
GLORIA: You matter.
and your story matters.
If you are just joining us.
I am here with Sue Buttons.
Is there a link
between the disappearance
of Sue's husband Karl.
- and the disappearance...
- (DOOR OPENS)
- ...of 13-year-old Emma Rose?
- (DOOR CLOSES)
And you're sure you heard him
say the name Emma Rose?
- How could you do this to me?
- (PAUSES VIDEO)
- What?
- You gave the story to Gloria Michaels?
Sue. this was my story.
Nancy. my husband is missing.
This isn't just a story.
Unbelievable.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
How are you holding up?
(SIGHS)
- I'm okay.
- Mm.
My friend Janet
made this for me.
- Well. that's nice.
- Mm-hm.
That was nice of her.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
(SIGHS)
I'm just happy you're here.
Oh. Sue. of course.
(NANCY SIGHS)
Do you remember
when you were little
and you would hold my hand
when I would walk you
to school?
And you would
squeeze it so tight
whenever we walked by a dog
because you were sure they were
all out to get you.
And then one day
I was dropping you off.
and Shelley Davis said.
"Your big sister is not pretty."
And you said. "Yeah.
she's just my half-sister."
And then you
stopped holding my hand.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Yes. this is Sue Buttons.
- (STARTS VIDEO)
- SUE: (ON VIDEO) ...Emma Rose.
Why didn't you
immediately call the police?
I didn't think
anything of it. I...
Tomorrow's fine with me.
I don't watch TV. so I hadn't
heard about poor Emma Rose.
(SUE STUTTERING ON VIDEO)
I only heard her name when
I was in your station today.
and that's when I...
I put two and two together.
GLORIA: Even if you
didn't know who Emma Rose...
Hey. Sue. Didn't you know
who Emma Rose was?
What?
Before you went
to Gloria Michaels.
when you and I were together.
you called her
"the missing girl."
That was Emma Rose's
parents on the phone.
Wow. Wait. what...
What did they want?
They-they want to meet me...
to talk.
Okay. I know what to do.
We're-we're gonna do
a joint interview
while there's still buzz about
a possible connection
between Karl and Emma.
I... I don't know.
Sue. the media
is your best friend right now.
The bigger the story.
the bigger the chances
of finding Karl and Emma.
Okay.
Yes! Ooh! Yes. yes. yes!
Okay. I'm gonna do
the whole thing.
and we're gonna
solve this together.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Go ahead!
(ALARM BLARING)
RITA: Go. Petey!
Come on. Petey. let's go!
(GRUNTING)
(RITA WHOOPING)
Ooh. I'm a criminal!
Oh. man!
(RITA CONTINUES WHOOPING)
PETEY: Shh! Stop making sounds!
We're gonna be dead
if you don't shut up!
- RITA: Come on. Petey!
- Stop saying my name!
RITA: Whoo! I feel so alive!
Let's do it again. Petey!
Hi. there.
Hi.
What can I get you?
I want a new TV.
Do I know you from somewhere?
You look very familiar.
I'm Sue. Sue-Sue Buttons.
(GASPS) Oh. my God. yes!
Oh. bless your heart.
Your husband Karl
was kidnapped.
That's right.
I want to make love
to this bag of bling.
We should keep some
for our ladies.
Deb would have
sex with me so hard
if I gave her a diamond.
No. come on. You can't keep
the shit you steal.
That's how
they catch you. okay?
Karl and I would
watch TV together every morning.
and our TV was destroyed
during the abduction.
And I just want something
to go back to normal.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Oh. no. Not at all.
I can't imagine
what you're going through.
I tell you.
if anybody ever hurt my Rita.
I would stab 'em
right in the heart.
Now let's get you a TV.
Okay. Okay.
This looks like at least
20 grand. right?
So I'll set a drop.
I'll give them the jewels.
I'll get Karl.
Everything will be back
to normal in the end.
Just put that shit away. please.
DEBBIE: (IN SING-SONG VOICE)
Petey? Order's going out.
PETEY: Shit. it's Sue.
What is she doing here?
Have you talked to her yet?
What do you want me to say?
"Hey. it's been awhile.
By the way. I'm the reason
your husband got kidnapped.
Well. I wouldn't
lead with that.
But you can tell her
we're handling things.
(SIGHS) Poor thing
looks so sad on TV.
Just put that shit away. please.
I'm gonna get you some
hard sex too. Petey. (CHUCKLES)
Hey. Sue!
Peter. what are you
doing here?
(PETEY SIGHS)
I work here now.
Let me give you a hand.
I got it. (GRUNTS)
How are you holding up
with everything. huh?
Not great.
- I'm gonna get Karl back.
- What?
How? I mean...
Do you know where he is?
No. I don't know where he is.
Or who took him
or why or anything.
- Do you know anything?
- No. I don't know anything.
Me neither.
I don't know anything.
But I just want you to know
that I am...
handling it.
I'm gonna get Karl back.
- (GASPS)
- Hey!
Uh. we're looking for Karl.
Karl is missing.
Oh.
Do you have any idea
where he's gone missing to?
No. Who-who-who are you?
(GRUNTS)
You don't know where Karl is?
No.
Are you sure?
(SOFTLY) Yes.
Where'd you get the money.
uh. to buy this?
I used. uh. my credit card.
I got a five percent discount.
You can...
You can have it. Please.
(RAY GRUNTS)
(SUE GROANS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Come on in here.
We want to find Karl.
Me. too.
Do you. um...
want us to help you find Karl?
(GAGS)
- What?
- (CHOKING)
- (EXHALES DEEPLY)
- Yes.
All right.
We'll help you find Karl.
Are you afraid?
Yes.
All right... (MUTTERS)
And you'll call us
if you hear from Karl. right?
NANCY: Okay.
- Hey.
- MAKE-UP ARTIST: Look at me.
- How you holding up?
- I'm good.
NANCY:
You seem a little. uh. jumpy.
Donna. she's fine.
She looks great.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- She's fine. Thank you. Bye-bye.
We're gonna do this
together. okay?
- Lennie! Get the damn door!
- Okay. okay.
I don't want
to do this anymore.
No. no. no. no. Sue. Sue.
Don't do this to me.
Not now. Sue.
Sue. you said that Karl
knew who took Emma.
Listen.
we'll get to all of that
when-when the cameras
are rolling.
Why don't you mic 'em.
Lennie. okay? Thank you.
Sue. hi.
Are you gonna be
on the news again today?
NANCY: Who's that?
I don't know.
but she fine as hell.
Quality Times Motel.
Ring a bell?
(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
NANCY: Sue? Are you okay?
She's an old friend.
(WHISPERS) Yes.
I'll be right back. Excuse me.
No. Sue. I'm begging you.
Sue. I'm begging you...
I said I'll be right back!
I'll be back. I'm sorry.
Can we just
talk outside a minute?
I'd love that.
SUE: Okay.
- What are you doing here?
- Where's the money?
What money?
Maybe I go on the news. too.
Tell them what
really happened to Karl.
- No. no. no.
- Get your hands off me.
I can tell everyone
about Karl.
- So don't fuck with me!
- Hey!
I'm sorry.
but I'm sure you're forgetting
that you don't know anything
about Karl.
Maybe I go to the police.
Don't you forget.
I'm doing you a favor.
Or do you want the world
and your kids to know
it was your poisonous vagina
that killed my husband.
I don't think you do.
So. as I said.
you know nothing about Karl.
I don't have any kids.
My husband does.
but fun fact.
I don't care
what his kids think.
I will tell your husband.
Go right ahead.
He's away on business.
but I can give you his number.
You can tell him
how you caught us cheating.
how Karl died.
how you did something
with his body.
and then reported him missing.
I'll get a divorce.
and you'll go to jail.
I am important.
I am strong.
I am enough!
Don't you think so. Sue?
(LEAH GASPS)
I want that money.
I swear these
White bitches are crazy.
SUE:
Hi. Mina. This is Sue.
I think I know someone
who can help you find Karl.
Her name is Leah.
And she drives a white Mercedes.
License plate one-three-Y...
...Quebec. Tango. three.
Detective Harris.
- Hey.
- Hi. How are you?
Have you had a break
in the case?
Not yet. I'm just checking in.
I'm sick with worry.
but I'm holding up okay.
I mean. the community
has been really supportive.
Yeah. Who's the lady
you were talking to?
An old friend.
That didn't look like
a friendly conversation.
Well. she hasn't made the time
to show her support
like others have.
My friend Janet.
she made me a casserole.
Oh. I love a casserole.
I shouldn't have
snapped at her.
It's just.
I can't expect everyone
to drop their lives
and rush to my aid
because my husband is missing.
Yeah. So listen. do you have
any new information for me? Hm?
Or am I gonna have to
find it out on the news tonight
- with the rest of the world?
- Oh.
Nothing new. unfortunately.
We're just doing everything
we can to raise awareness.
I-I should probably
get back inside.
but thank you for stopping by.
Detective Harris.
When did you eat the cake?
I'm sorry?
You said you didn't have time
to celebrate
your birthday that night.
and when you woke up.
Karl was gone. so...
When did you eat the cake?
I... You know...
I guess Karl
must've snuck a piece
before he was taken.
Detective Harris...
(SIGHS)
Please find my husband.
and bring him home.
I just want my husband back.
I'll do all I can. all right.
Mrs. Buttons?
SUE: Thank you. Detective.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Mr. and Mrs. Rose. please!
- What's going on?
- We can't do this.
We just want
our little girl back.
They lost their nerve
waiting on you.
I needed this interview!
I'm sorry. but Detective Harris
came by to check in.
We can still do the interview.
No. we can't. We can't do the
interview without the Roses.
The Roses were the hook!
No one wants to watch
just you!
(GROANS) Sue. Sue!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That was... That was
really stupid of me to say.
Listen. let's just...
Let's just do the interview. okay?
No. It's okay.
I think it would be best for me
to do my interviews
with Gloria Michaels anyway.
She'll reach
a larger audience... for Karl.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Fuck.
Thank you for coming.
I won't be filming today.
So. you can
let yourselves out.
Thank you.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
You are powerful.
You are strong.
You don't need the Roses.
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
I just had... (MUTTERS)
Where's the "W"?
Upside-down. It looks like...
REPORTER:
Apparently. a ransom note
was sent to the wife
of Karl Buttons
demanding $50.000
for his return.
Karl was reported missing
yesterday morning
by his wife. Sue.
Who are you. Leah Norton?
- JONES: No. thank you for calling.
- HARRIS: Okay.
- Thanks so much.
- JONES: Yeah. Yeah. I got
The numbers came in
from the bank.
Missing banker Karl's
been up to no good.
He's been laundering money
through the bank for months now.
And this was taken
the day Karl went missing.
- HARRIS: Hm.
- The guys that killed Steve
definitely met with Karl
the day he disappeared.
(CHUCKLES) All right.
I don't need a gold star.
but I think we can both admit
this is a major break.
- Harris.
- Oh. hey. Captain Riggins.
Have you been following
Sue Buttons?
Sitting outside her house?
I've been working my case.
By harassing the victim's wife?
Her sister's a reporter.
We do not need more bad press.
Okay... Captain.
She canceled dinner reservations
the night that Karl disappeared.
Who cancels dinner plans
unless you know your husband
isn't gonna be there?
And-and then there's the cake.
Cake and dinner reservations?
That's your evidence?
- Captain...
- RIGGINS: Officer Jones.
do you share
Detective Harris' feeling?
Well. I definitely think
Mrs. Buttons is strange.
But. no. I don't think
she has anything to do
with her husband's
disappearance.
Right now. our strongest lead
is the bank.
Karl was laundering money.
and he's somehow
connected to these men
that we believe
killed Steve Perkins.
And that is actual evidence.
- Sue...
- Stand down. Harris.
Or you're off the case.
DISPATCHER: (ON SPEAKER)
Captain Riggins.
your wife is here to see you.
(WHISPERS) Fuck.
Look. right now. I just think
we need to focus on the bank
and see where it goes.
I am the senior officer
on this case. okay.
You back me up!
RITA: Petey.
Hey. Rita.
I can see the bag.
Are you trying to sneak off
to this ransom drop without me?
I thought we were partners.
Look. they told me
to come alone. all right.
Everyone knows that you're
supposed to pretend to go alone
but actually bring backup
to wait nearby
in case something goes down.
That's ransom drop 101.
Look. I can close up while...
No! Rita! You're not coming!
This is not a game.
- Fine.
- All right. You're not coming.
Well. at least take my gun.
No. I'm not taking a gun.
You mean to tell me
you gonna go to a ransom drop
- with no backup and no gun?
- Yeah.
What a dumbass.
Police!
Ms. Norton? Anybody home?
(DOG PANTING)
Hey.
Where's your mama. little baby?
Huh? She in here?
Jesus Christ.
Well. that's a lot of dicks.
Ugh! Quality Times Motel?
Well. you're a dirty girl.
aren't you. Ms. Norton.
RAY: We don't got time for this.
(TIRES SCREECH)
MINA: Took you long enough.
PETEY: I'm sorry.
We were just about to go
kill Karl.
- Oh. no. Don't do that.
- You got the money?
Yeah. right here.
What the fuck is this?
That's gotta be worth
at least 20 grand.
- Probably more.
- Is that an opal?
Yes. ma'am. It's the best
I could do on such short notice.
- All right.
- Please.
You know what?
I'm feeling hospitable.
I'll take it.
So you're gonna
let Karl go now?
Obviously. Yeah.
That-that's how ransom works.
You know what ransom is. right?
I do know how it works
and what it means. Thank you.
Easiest 20 grand
I have ever made.
Now maybe you can focus on
getting your daddy's
millions back.
Can you. uh. not kill my vibe?
It's a good day.
Don't you think
it's a good day?
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- No?
That's too bad.
'Cause I'm having a really good day.
(WHIRRING)
Hey. Dad.
I got a present for you.
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
- (WHIRRING STOPS)
- (LEAH WHIMPERING)
MINA: It's the mistress.
The wife put us onto her.
(SCREAMS)
Please. tell Sue I'm sorry.
Where's Karl?
I won't tell anyone about Karl.
I promise.
What do you know about Karl?!
I don't know anything!
(DRAWER SLIDES OPEN)
Wait. wait. wait!
What do you want me to say?
I will say
whatever you want me to say!
(SOBBING) Please.
Cut off her fingers.
No! Wait! Wait!
Holy. holy. holy shit!
(SOBBING)
Why are you doing this?
We don't have any money.
Karl was actually kidnapped.
- SUE: Please. let him go.
- He was actually kidnapped.
LEAH: No. don't touch me!
Don't touch me! No!
Just tie her to the chair.
SUE:
Thank you for coming. I...
It means a lot to me.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING ON TV)
I'm so sorry. I'm so...
I'm weak with exhaustion.
and I need to go inside
and pray.
Mmm. Look how
they capture the emotion.
Please continue
to pray for Karl.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- (REPORTERS CLAMORING)
- Thank you.
(TV TURNS OFF)
(KNOCKING)
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS)
What does she want?
Answer this door!
Yes. Detective Harris?
Where is she?
Who?
I saw you arguing with her.
and now she's gone.
Where is she?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You need to come down
to the station with me.
Am I under arrest?
Then I am not going down
to the police station
with you.
- Turn around.
- What?
Put your hands behind your back.
I'm detaining you
for questioning
in the disappearing
of Karl Buttons and Leah Norton.
You're gonna regret this.
Detective Harris.
- Oh. yeah? Fuck you.
- Ow.
Okay. Sue. I'm real sorry.
I forgot your birthday.
That was really shitty of me.
(HARRIS MUTTERING)
Ow. ow. ow. ow. ow!
Oh. my purse.
Aren't you gonna read me
my rights?
You have the right
to shut the fuck up.
- SUE: These are really pinching.
- HARRIS: Good.
- Ow. ow. ow. ow!
- Just get inside.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Hello.
Hey. Lennie. did you get
the video I sent you?
In the two seconds
since you sent it to me? No.
All right. hold on.
Let me look.
HARRIS: You have the right
to shut the fuck up.
- Oh. my God.
- SUE: Ow. ow. ow. ow. ow!
- Why was Sue arrested?
- NANCY: Do what I say.
and tip off Gloria Michaels.
Wait. you-you wanna
give away our lead?
Just do it.
- Load up.
- Right now? We're eating lunch.
Load up! Do your damn job.
They told me they let him go.
I told you.
you should've brought my gun.
You can't go to a ransom drop
without a gun.
- They lied!
- Bad guys lie. Petey.
Rain is wet. Shit stinks.
What else is obvious?
All right. that's it.
I'm going to the police.
You can't do that.
I should've gone to them
in the first place.
Well. yeah. you should.
but you didn't.
And if you go to
the police now.
they're gonna have
a lot of questions.
Like. where'd you get the 20.000
to pay the first ransom?
Well. I can't just do nothing.
Rita.
I never said
we were gonna do nothing.
- Hmm?
- An eye for an eye. Petey.
An eye for an eye.
Can you step
out of the way. honey?
(SIGHS)
Let's set up right here.
We'll need you to clear.
Oh. my God.
That's fucking Gloria Michaels.
HARRIS: You know what. I get it.
He was cheating on you.
With Leah.
But you knew that.
You knew that
You're the kind of woman.
you could accept an affair.
Well. until you couldn't.
It was your birthday.
and he bought flowers
for some other bitch.
I'da killed him too.
I woulda grabbed him
by his baby dick. got my gun.
and I woulda shot him up
the piss hole.
What is this shit?
Channel Five?
Damn news people.
(EXHALES)
(SUE SOBBING)
- (REPORTERS CLAMORING)
- (SUE CONTINUES SOBBING)
GLORIA: Detective Harris.
why did you arrest Sue Buttons?
Do you think
she had something to do
with the disappearance
of her husband. Karl.
Gloria. I don't... I don't know
why this is happening to me.
I've done nothing wrong.
Help me. Ms. Michaels.
REPORTER 1: Miss Buttons...
Please. Ms. Michaels. help me.
REPORTER 2: Detective Harris.
what charges is she facing?
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Would you stay off my ass.
Reggie? Jesus!
JONES: Harris!
- Harris!
- No.
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
- What are you doing?
- No!
Okay. Now tell me what happened
the night of your birthday.
I think every station was there.
(SIGHS)
You said you fell asleep
as soon as you got home.
Yes. (SIGHS)
But I know you
called La Femme Aimée.
and you canceled your dinner
reservation later that night.
Oh. uh. yes.
I must have called
before I fell asleep.
Then why'd you cancel
your dinner reservations?
I suppose because we
weren't having dinner anymore.
When we questioned you.
you said.
"It was my birthday.
and we had dinner reservations.
But I must have fallen asleep.
because then it was morning
and I knew something was wrong
because Karl never woke me.
Yes.
But now you're saying you
weren't going to dinner.
- So which is it?
- What?
Well. were you going to dinner
or weren't you going to dinner?
Mrs. Buttons?
You're-you're
trying to confuse me.
Truth is never confusing.
(VOICE BREAKING)
My husband is missing.
There are no cameras
in here. Sue.
I don't want to talk to you.
This is... This is harassment.
Harris!
HARRIS:
Captain. I'm in the middle
- of an interrogation.
- RIGGINS: Now.
I told you to stand down!
Captain. uh... I have her.
Just give me 20 minutes.
I've got Gloria fucking Michaels
on our doorstep.
She-she killed her husband
and Leah Norton.
- Who?
- Leah Norton.
I saw her arguing with her
in the yard yesterday.
And-and-and I traced her
license plates.
I went to her house.
and she's gone.
Her car is in the driveway.
Her stove is on.
The-the purse.
the keys. everything.
It's there. but she's gone.
And I think she was
having an affair with Karl.
I think Sue found out.
and I think that
she's done something with her.
Does she have a dog?
Is it possible she was walking
her dog. or buying milk.
or any other fucking thing.
minding her own
goddamn business.
while you were performing
an illegal
and unauthorized search
of her home?!
- Captain...
- You are off the case.
No. Captain.
she killed her husband!
Mrs. Buttons.
I have your purse.
I know I'm right. Jones.
I think you
believe you're right.
When your partner believes
they're right... you trust it.
Good luck.
Fuck. Petey.
Scream and you're dead.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I'll make a brief statement.
Mrs. Buttons is not.
and has never been.
considered a suspect
in her husband's disappearance.
- (CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
- Captain Riggins. why was Sue
brought into your station
in handcuffs?
This has all been
a misunderstanding.
Now. we don't wanna hurt you.
Well. you're gonna
die tonight!
- You're gonna die tonight!
- Nobody's dying tonight!
- You're gonna die!
- Just...
- Hey. hey. hey. hey!
We're just gonna call the boss.
Make an even exchange.
So everybody just chill out!
Yeah. yeah. Chill out!
Or I'll chill you out.
You're not gonna do shit.
old lady.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (SCREAMS)
- PETEY: Holy shit!
- Oh. my fucking ear!
- You shot my fucking ear off!
- PETEY: Oh. shit!
- Take this. Talk to him.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- I'll keep her quiet.
- I'm... (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(IN RASPY VOICE)
We have your daughter.
- MR. KIM: Mina?
- Release your hostage.
- (MINA SCREAMING)
- Mina!
RITA: Or we will kill her.
Oh. I'm gonna rip
your fucking throat...
Next time.
it's gonna be your face!
- (CELL PHONE CHIMING)
- Goddamnit. (GRUNTS)
I gotta go. Jonelle.
- What you mean you gotta go?
- I gotta go.
Jonelle's in labor!
Would you mind
if I held onto this?
Yes! I do mind!
Okay. You know. you are right.
This belongs to you.
This is yours...
(GASPS)
Who do you work for?
- What?
- Her people have Mina.
What? No!
I don't have any people.
I... (GASPS)
Where's my daughter?
Who do you work for?!
LEAH: What are you doing? No!
(GROANS)
Where is my daughter?
It was Sue! Karl's wife!
She killed Karl.
and she took your money.
- Sue has my money?
- There was a bag full of money!
Karl said it was
three million dollars.
And she has my daughter?
Karl's idiot brother. Petey.
Mina told him we had Karl.
I should have stopped her.
I told you
I don't have people!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I have kids! I have kids!
Please!
Me. too.
- (LEAH SCREAMING)
- (WHIRRING)
(SQUISHING)
- PETEY: Jonelle! Hey!
- Hey.
(PANTING)
Hey. I'm here.
You okay? Let's go!
I made eggplant parm.
Wait. What is going on?
You said you were in labor.
Oh. yeah. I lied.
- What?
- I lied.
Sit down. baby.
We should really eat this
before it gets cold.
Jesus Christ. Jo. what's...
Now we're both liars.
Now. what do you mean by that?
What do I mean by that?
Fucking Rita.
Petey. get out!
Okay. wait. Please.
Listen. you can have me.
the babies.
homemade eggplant parm.
or you can have your stealing
and your secrets.
and your scary bad guys.
- but you can't have both.
- They have Karl!
- What?
- Ray and Mina kidnapped Karl.
and I needed the money
to pay his ransom.
Baby. they have my brother.
And they wouldn't
if it weren't for me.
JONELLE: I care about you.
I care about the twins.
I care about our family.
I don't care about Karl.
Petey. what do you care about?
RITA: (ON VOICEMAIL) You have
reached Rita's cellular phone.
Please leave a message.
Hey. Rita. Give me a call back
when you get this. I think...
(PETEY SIGHS)
It's time
we went to the police.
So in a shootout.
do you look at what you're shooting at.
or do you just close your eyes
and hope you hit something?
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Oh. I gotta...
Don't move.
(RINGING CONTINUES)
(GUNSHOT)
Next time. try saving me
before they shoot
my fucking ear off!
We gotta take care of Petey.
Your daddy wants you to go home.
- I'm gonna take care of Petey.
- Fuck no!
RAY: You've caused enough
problems for one day. Go home.
- No!
- Stay here if you want.
You're not coming with me.
Stop being dumb. dude.
Put that out.
MINA: Don't worry.
I won't set us on fire.
RAY: Grow up.
MINA: Why?
(SCREAMING)
- (MINA GRUNTS)
- (GAGGING)
Rita...
My Rita.
(GROANS)
Shut it.
All this trouble for 20 grand.
How could she think I could do
such terrible things?
I'll give you a ride home.
Oh. no. it's okay.
My sister's here.
Captain Riggins? Thank you.
You came for me.
Yeah. of course.
(SIGHS) Sue...
NANCY: I knew
the captain would let you go
once Gloria Michaels arrived.
Why are we stopping?
What are you doing?
(SIGHS)
What happened to Karl?
I know.
Sue. if you did something.
I can help you.
- What?
- But I need to know what happened.
I need to know everything.
Wow. Wow.
You know. you're-you're
a real piece of work. Nancy.
You were miked.
What are you talking about?
- LEAH: Where's the money?
- SUE: What money?
LEAH: Maybe I go on TV. too.
Tell them what
really happened to Karl.
- SUE: No. no. no. no. no.
- LEAH: Get your hands off me.
I found this when I was
going through the audio.
SUE: I can tell
everyone about Karl.
So don't fuck with me!
You must be mistaken.
Fucking damn it. Sue. please.
- SUE: Let me go!
- Sue.
Sue! Sue. where are you going?
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I want to help you!
I don't need you
to tell my story!
I don't want
to tell your story!
I just want to be your sister!
We can still fix this.
Sue. but first. you gotta stop
talking to the press.
Oh. There it is.
There what is?
You're mad
because I didn't invite you
to my press conference.
Oh. my God. Sue.
This is serious.
- You can go to jail for this.
- You're jealous
because everyone's
paying attention to me now.
You're jealous because I'm
the more popular sister now.
Oh. my God. do you
hear how crazy you sound?
I hope a dog bites you
in the face.
Real nice.
Sue. Sue.
- Oh. my God!
- (SUE YELLS)
Open the door!
Nancy. go away!
Real nice. Sue.
Open the fucking door!
Please. I want to help you.
Nancy. please. just go away.
NANCY: Come on.
Hi. Nancy.
Why don't you stay?
Where's my money?
What money?
You mistake me
for a patient man.
I will ask you once more.
and you will not make
the same mistake.
Karl took my money. where is it?
NANCY: Sue...
(WHISPERS)
Sue. tell him the truth.
Karl's missing. I...
(STUTTERS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Shut up!
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
- Fuck!
- Wait! Wait!
- Shut up!
Wait! I'll tell you where Karl is!
I know where he is!
I'll tell you.
My sister has nothing
to do with this.
You leave her out of it.
You hear me?
NANCY: (CRYING) Oh. fuck!
Please. just let her go.
and I'll tell you.
- Oh. my God!
- Please. just let her go.
NANCY: Sue...
SUE: I'm so sorry. Nancy.
(NANCY CONTINUES CRYING)
(HORN HONKS)
Harris.
You following me?
Yeah. Just hang on. Hey.
Look... I haven't had your back.
And I'm sorry.
Look. I trust
your instincts as...
I ain't got time
for apologies.
Officer Jones.
You coming?
Get out.
Shovel.
- Where?
- It's over there.
Go.
(DINGS BELL)
Would you two like a room?
No. um. we're here
about an investigation.
- Oh.
- Do you recognize any of these people?
Oh. goodness.
I'm not too good with faces.
Not like my Charlie was.
Why. he could remember a face
from way. way...
Okay. So this would've been
from three nights ago.
Let me see.
Well. if you say
they were here.
then I suppose
I must have seen them.
Sorry. Harris.
Yeah.
Can I see
your security footage?
Security footage?
Oh. goodness. yeah.
This is not funny.
Rita. call me back. (GROANS)
WOMAN: (ON TV)
What do I always say?
- Maybe you should just go.
- "Batter matters."
I don't know.
something isn't right.
- ...it's all about the egg.
- I know.
See how deep-yellow
these yolks are?
I'm gonna be straight with you.
The paler the egg yolk.
the better the chances are
that egg came from
a chicken who was cooped up.
PETEY: I'm sorry.
Maybe we just
don't get to be normal.
PETEY: Let me go find Rita.
I'll be right back.
JONELLE: Okay.
I will. Be right back.
(TV CONTINUES PLAYING
INDISTINCTLY)
(WHISPERS) Okay.
(TIRES SCREECH)
PETEY: Oh. my... Shit!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Baby. please pick up.
(SIRENS WAILING)
WOMAN: (ON TV)
He's not quite one year old.
and he weighs about 24 pounds.
Which makes handling
this adorable puppy...
RITA: (ON TV) No. charge.
It comes with the couch.
TVs.
You gotta eat.
No credit. no...
PETEY: Baby. pick up!
(GUN COCKS)
(RAY GROANING)
(JONELLE PANTING)
(JONELLE YELLING)
I'm fucking pregnant!
Asshole!
We're gonna have twins!
And we're gonna get married!
And we're gonna be happy!
(SOBBING)
HARRIS: Look. That's Sue!
- We got her!
- No. you got her.
Fuck yeah. I did!
(LAUGHING)
- Come on. Let's go.
- All right.
Hey. pretty girl!
We got her!
Thank you. ma'am.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
My goodness. you...
Y'all have a good night.
- JONES: Have a good night.
- HARRIS: Yeah. you too.
Bye-bye.
That's a murder investigation.
- All right. I'll see you there.
- Okay.
(THUDDING)
(WHISPERS) Hey.
Come on.
- Jonelle!
- (JONELLE CRYING)
Baby! Hey.
Hey. hey. hey.
We're gonna get out of here.
We are gonna move away.
and we are gonna be happy.
I promise you.
- (CONTINUES CRYING)
- Come here...
You could be famous
as the man
who found Karl Buttons.
We could... we could be
on the news together.
The bag.
(GRUNTS)
- (CHUCKLES)
- SUE: Oh. my God. I...
I didn't know.
Back in the hole.
I-I can help you.
I can... I can tell your story.
Wouldn't you like that?
No thanks.
No. no. no!
No! Please. don't!
- Police!
- Drop it!
- Drop your fucking gun!
- Drop your weapon!
- (SUE SCREAMING)
- (GROANS)
- Jones!
- SUE: I'm sorry.
HARRIS: Don't move!
Drop your shovel.
Drop your shovel!
Please. I...
I'm sorry about your partner.
Get on your fucking knees.
and put your hands
above your head!
I... You saved me.
I'm gonna tell them
you saved me
at the...
at the next press conference.
No more press conferences
for you. Sue!
- (GRUNTS)
- (HARRIS SCREAMS)
- (SCREAMS)
- SUE: No. no. no...
No. no.
(HARRIS GROANING)
No. no. no. no. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
I didn't.
I'll tell everyone
that you saved me.
and you'll be famous
and no one will forget you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Fuck you.
(GROANING)
SUE: My story matters.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I am enough.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
I am confident.
My life
is unfolding beautifully.
REPORTER: This is Channel Five
with breaking news.
Thirteen-year-old Emma Rose
was found alive and well today
at a bus stop
in Miami. Florida.
Her relieved family says
she had apparently run away
from home.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
GLORIA: It was a weekend
of horror for Sue Buttons.
A weekend of chaos and loss.
A weekend many of us
in her position
would not have survived.
But you did survive.
And you had the courage
to share your story.
A year ago. I lived through
the worst three days
of my life.
I lost my husband.
I thought my life was over.
But through my daily
affirmations.
I was able to find
my inner strength to keep going.
And I wanted to give
that power to others.
So I wrote a book.
A New York Times
best-selling book.
Take Your Life Back.
America. I'd like you
to meet my friend. Sue Buttons.
Hello. America.
It's nice to meet you.
(LIVELY INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
Now. you have a quote
on the cover of this book
that says.
"If you make them see you.
they will finally look."
Tell me about that.
That's right.
That quote is so special to me.
It came to me in a dream.
Dreams are so important.
I'm writing a book.
I made that decision
right now.
It's called Dreamscape.
- (LAUGHS) I love it.
- It's like escaping.
- Yes. That's lovely.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna say this
right here and now.
I think I have
another book in me.
So perhaps we can
go on a book tour together.
- Oh...
- I haven't thought of my title yet.
It might be
Continue Taking Your Life...
Back?
Oh. yes. of course. (CHUCKLES)
Of course. Back.
Take Your Life Back.
Continue Taking Your Life Back.
(WHISPERS) You're so brave.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull